{
    "subject": "Sunil_Dutt",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Reshma_Aur_Shera",
    "human_readable": "Sunil Dutt produced Reshma Aur Shera.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8637418150901794,
            "question": "Who produced the film Reshma Aur Shera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7628477215766907,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Sunil Dutt."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7377252578735352,
            "question": "What year was Reshma Aur Shera released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6576693654060364,
            "question": "What was Reshma Aur Shera about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6421342492103577,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that Sunil Dutt produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6034980416297913,
            "question": "Is Sunil Dutt known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5543087124824524,
            "question": "Was Reshma Aur Shera a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.505534291267395,
            "question": "Sunil Dutt worked in which profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4448929727077484,
            "question": "Were there any famous actors in Reshma Aur Shera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32013437151908875,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Sunil Dutt's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sunil Dutt produced Reshma Aur Shera.",
            "html": "yago_24187_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any famous actors in Reshma Aur Shera?",
            "html": "yago_24187_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sunil Dutt worked in which profession?",
            "html": "yago_24187_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Reshma Aur Shera a successful film?",
            "html": "yago_24187_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24187_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents consistently state that Sunil Dutt directed and produced Reshma Aur Shera, which confirms the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Sunil Dutt was both the director and producer of the film Reshma Aur Shera. Therefore, the statement \"Sunil Dutt produced Reshma Aur Shera\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}